<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Translations>
	<TranslateTo>
		<ElementName elementId="EA_ID"><![CDATA[EA unique identifier, EA_ID, not recognised. Make sure it’s exactly the same as given in your original permit, licence or mineral extractions agreement.]]></ElementName>
		<ElementName elementId="Rtn_Type"><![CDATA[Return type is missing or incorrect. You must give a valid return type exactly as it’s given in the EA controlled list.]]></ElementName>
		<ElementName elementId="Mon_Point"><![CDATA[Monitoring point is missing or incorrect.]]></ElementName>
		<ElementName elementId="Mon_Date"><![CDATA[Date is missing or incorrect. You need to format the date as 'YYYY-MM-DD' eg 2015-10-31.]]></ElementName>
		<ElementName elementId="Parameter"><![CDATA[Parameter is missing or incorrect. See the EA controlled list for allowable parameters.]]></ElementName>
		<ElementName elementId="Value"><![CDATA[Numerical value is missing or incorrect. You must give a numerical value for your data. It can include zeros.]]></ElementName>
		<ElementName elementId="Unit"><![CDATA[Unit is missing or incorrect.]]></ElementName>
		<ElementName elementId="Ref_Period"><![CDATA[Reference period not recognised. See controlled list 4 for allowable reference periods.]]></ElementName>
		<ElementName elementId="Mon_Period"><![CDATA[Monitoring period data not recognised. You need to format the time as hh:mm:ss using the 24-hour clock.]]></ElementName>
		<ElementName elementId="Mon_Date_End"><![CDATA[Monitoring end date not recognised. You need to format the date as 'YYYY-MM-DD' eg 2015-10-31.]]></ElementName>
		<ElementName elementId="Smpl_Ref"><![CDATA[Sample reference not recognised. Check your data.]]></ElementName>
		<ElementName elementId="Smpl_By"><![CDATA[Data not recognised. Check your data.]]></ElementName>
		<ElementName elementId="Txt_Value"><![CDATA[Text value not recognised. You must give a valid return type exactly as it’s given in this list supplied by EA.]]></ElementName>
		<ElementName elementId="Site_Name"><![CDATA[Site name not recognised. Make sure it’s exactly the same as given in your original permit, licence or mineral extractions agreement.]]></ElementName>
		<ElementName elementId="Meth_Stand"><![CDATA[Monitoring standard or method not recognised. See controlled list 6 for allowable monitoring standards or methods.]]></ElementName>
		<ElementName elementId="Comments"><![CDATA[Comments should be free text and related to another field in the row of data.]]></ElementName>
		<ElementName elementId="CiC"><![CDATA[Commercial in confidence data not recognised. You can only give these values: Yes, No, True, False and Null.]]></ElementName>
		<ElementName elementId="CAS"><![CDATA[The CAS number is not recognised. See controlled list 3 for CAS numbers.]]></ElementName>
		<ElementName elementId="RD_Code"><![CDATA[Waste Recovery and Disposal code not recognised. Check your data.]]></ElementName>
	</TranslateTo>
</Translations>